You're sending me away to Saga?
That's right. It's where Master Hebea was born.
If I'm not mistaken, I believe that his wife passed away a long time ago,
so it should be quite a peaceful arrangement.
Honestly, I'm relieved.
Up against him, even the most notable dignitaries won't make a fuss.
He has wisdom and experience on his side,
and, well, you would know more about these matters than I could explain.
Proprietor, Madam, you have my thanks. I appreciate all that you've done.
In my years, I've never seen a courtesan like you before, Yugiiri.
And I'm afraid we never will again.
To gain so much popularity, she could no longer get customers? Unheard of.
I'm sorry if I have caused you any trouble.
I wish you the best life.
But knowing you, I shouldn't have cause to worry.
Oh my goodness, what have you girls been doing?
Yugiiri, are you leaving us? Will we see you again? Is Saga really far away?
Please don't go. I wanted you to teach me more about singing and dancing.
There, there, girls. She's a legendary courtesan who's starting a new life for herself.
You should be happy for her.
Come now. Don't cry. Now. Let me see you smile.
I may be far away in Saga, but I promise that each of you will remain close to my heart.
Well, technically, Saga doesn't actually exist anymore.
Huh?